myinfoline.com 2015-03-28

# Privacy | MyInfoline India | MyInfoline Yellow Page | Indian Business Directory | Yellow pages India

Thank you for visiting our website, and for viewing our [terms and conditions ](https://www.myinfoline.com/pages/termsandconditions)and our privacy policy published on this page. We welcome you aboard, and are looking forward to doing business together. Before you go further though, we ask that you take a few moments to review the brief information that follows. If you are unable to accept these terms, then we respectfully ask you to leave.

Like most other companies operating on the internet, **MY INFOLINE** (hereafter called “ **MY INFOLINE** ”) collects basic client information to make your experience the very best available on the internet. At the same time, we respect your privacy, and assure you that we will protect this information and use it responsibly.

We believe in providing a safe and secure browsing experience for all of our clients, through the application of stringent and effective security measures. These methods include storing your information on our own secure servers, and never sending personal information about you via email- such as your credit card details, your name, or your address.

**Browser Data Collection**  
**MY INFOLINE** gathers navigational data about where you go on our website. This information allows us to know which areas you visited most. This helps us to enhance the quality of your future online experiences, by providing more of the features, services and products that you prefer.  
We may also collect additional information that does not personally identify you (for example your domain type, your browser version, your service provider and your IP address). This provides further insight regarding your use of our website (such as the time and date of your last visit to a page).  
Should you access this website using a mobile device, then that device may disclose your contact number and your current physical location to us. You should adjust your settings to disable this feature if you do not want this to happen. However, knowing where you’re calling from helps us to refine our service to you even more.  
  
**Protection of Your Personal Information**  
When you establish or update your account with us, purchase credits online or provide information to us (for example your name, your address, your e-mail address and your credit card data) we store this in private files on our secure server and internal systems. **MY INFOLINE** uses this information to deliver even better service to you in the future.  
However, we do not store information provided by children whom we know to be under eighteen years of age, because this would contravene federal law.  
  
**Non-Disclosure of Your Personal Information**  
**MY INFOLINE** will never sell, rent or trade your email address to any third party. We may however employ third parties as an extension of our services (for example fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, and administering e-mails on our behalf).

In this case, we may provide such personally identifiable information about you as is necessary to them, for example your name, your address, your e-mail address, and your telephone number). When we do so, **MY INFOLINE** will instruct these third parties to maintain this information in the strictest confidence.

We may occasionally forward promotional offers to you by other businesses that we support, unless you [optout](https://myinfoline.com/home/optemail) of this opportunity. Please be assured that such communication is strictly between you and us, and that the only personal information these businesses may hold on you, is what you choose to tell them about yourself.

**Legal Requirements We Comply With**

**Cookies**  
**MY INFOLINE** assigns a unique identification to your computer, which helps us make our website more responsive, and generally deliver a better and more personalized experience. Cookies are normally stored on your computer’s hard drive, and help us track your mouse clicks as you go through the pages of this website.

They also help us to track the status of any service requests, and to confirm whether you have visited us before. The benefit to you is that it’s no longer necessary to keep on entering the same information over and over again (such as your name and email address).

Should you prefer not to benefit from the advantages cookies bring, then we recommend you use the facility you may have on your browser to disable them.This may restrict the usefulness of our service to you, because you might not be able to transact with usanymore.

**Offer, Discount and Cash Back Points**  
**My Infoline** is fully authorized to change in any kind of offer, discount and rules of cash back point without prior written to any members.

**Personal Information Updates**  
It’s in both our interests that you keep your personal information updated on our website, for example your billing information and your delivery address.Simply log on to our website, [check your data](https://www.myinfoline.com/member/dashboard), and modify it when convenient.

**Forums, Social Media Accounts and Discussion Boards**  
Any opinion expressed on our forums, social media accounts and discussion boards is the spontaneous, un-moderated opinion of its author, and published without review.Hence **MY INFOLINE** : makes no guarantees regarding the soundness of that opinion, nor necessarily agrees with it either.

While we do request that information published in this way be neither confidential nor offensive, we are unable to accept responsibility for its content, or the indirect or direct consequences thereof. If you are unable to accept this policy, then we respectfully request that you do not visit our forums, social media accounts and discussion boards, to ensure you are not affected.

**Link to Other Websites**  
**MY INFOLINE** provides links to other websites which we hope will enrich your browsing experience with us. However we are not responsible for those websites’ privacy practices. Therefore we recommend that you enquire about them on your first visit.
